pinvoke.net 2017-11-18

# Legal Information About Redgate Software

## Our privacy policy

### Introduction

Redgate (which means here Redgate Software Limited and its subsidiary Red Gate Software Inc.) respects your privacy. All information you give us is held with the utmost care and security.

Please take time to review this privacy policy as it sets out our privacy practices and tells you how your personal information will be treated by us. We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. Only in the circumstances described within this Privacy Policy would we share your information with any third party.

Our use of personal data in the UK is in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and our Subsidiary’s practices in the US are as far as reasonably possible in line with those in the UK.

Any questions regarding Redgate’s privacy policy should be directed to [privacy@red-gate.com](mailto:privacy@red-gate.com), or alternatively see the section Contacting us.

### Use of information

Redgate will not collect any personal information about individuals except as set out in this privacy policy.

Examples of the types of personal information we will collect are: name, company, postal address, email address, phone number, details of website, features and product usage, installation data and product commentary.

We will use the personal information provided to us in order to:

  * process orders submitted by you;
  * identify the Redgate 'certified partner' that is best placed to support your software purchase if you cannot purchase directly from us;
  * customize the service we provide to you;
  * administrate or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us;
  * verify your identity (e.g. if you participate in any promotions administered by us);
  * anticipate and resolve any problems with any goods or services supplied to you;
  * carry out market research and surveys and track sales data;
  * send you our newsletter, where this is requested by you;
  * track your engagement with us, including through our website, articles and newsletters;
  * understand how you use our products and services;
  * contact you by telephone and send you follow-up communications relating to your use of software downloaded from our website; and
  * send you information about our other products and services.

We may collect any personal information provided by you to us through this website or via use of our products, or we may collect this information via one of our telephone operators or through your email or other communications with us. We may collect anonymous answers to surveys or anonymous and aggregated information about how our products are used. Certain information is collected automatically, as described later in the privacy policy.

We may also ask you for other optional information such as what sort of equipment/device/software you use and what other subjects interest you. If you choose to give us this information, we will use it to help us to provide you with the best possible service that is personalized to your needs and preferences.

We may also combine personal information with Product Usage Data to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

Although we do not make it compulsory to give us every item of information we ask for, the more information volunteered by our customers (and the more accurate it is), the better we can match our services to the needs of the body of our customers.

During the installation process we may give you the opportunity to choose what ‘product use’ information you provide to us.

We also collect information from you if you choose to take part in any of our on-site surveys or promotions. We will use this information to administer the promotion, help us to plan other promotions and improve the services we provide.

### Information automatically collected about your use of Redgate Products

  * **Product Usage Data** – We collect product usage data which records certain 'in-product' actions and activities such as 'starting a product', 'creating a workflow', 'open a project', 'run deployment wizard', 'format SQL', 'autocomplete', and 'use a snippet'. We do not scan or collect the content of any file or information that might be displayed by an application or used whilst performing such actions or activities.

  * **Device Data** – We collect information about your computer, such as operating system, amount of memory, region, language, time zone, browser version, version of SQL Server.

  * **Error reports** – If you experience problems with our products we may collect data about the products and any problems you experience with them. This data helps us improve our products and services, to diagnose problems in the products you use, and provide solutions. Depending on your product and settings, error reports can include data such as the type or severity of the problem, details of the software or hardware related to an error, contents of files you were using when an error occurred and the current state of the software.

### Preview, Freeware and Free Edition Software

Redgate offers preview, freeware and free edition software or other optional features that will enable you to use them while providing feedback and usage data to Redgate.

As a result, these releases may automatically collect additional data, provide fewer controls, and otherwise employ different privacy and security measures than those typically present in our products. If you participate in previews or pre-release programs, we may contact you about your feedback or your interest in continuing to use the product after general release.

### Third-Parties and their sites

Certain Redgate services, such as payment processing, information processing or assisting with user evaluation of our products, are offered in conjunction with our (third-party) business partners. In such cases, we may need to share your personal information with them in order to provide these services. In this instance, please note that certain services may be unavailable if you do not want to disclose the personal information you are asked for.

Where our services make use of hosted tools, hosted data storage and payment services provided by third parties any of your personal information stored by such third parties shall be subject to their privacy provisions.

Whilst we choose our business partners carefully, unfortunately we cannot be responsible for their privacy policies and practices or those of other sites that you access using links from our site. Therefore we recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit.

In addition, if you linked to our site from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

### Call Recording

We record some calls for training and quality purposes to help us evaluate our performance in customer-orientated parts of the business. You have the right to choose not to be recorded.

### Log files/IP addresses

When you visit our website, we automatically log your IP address which is recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer the website, to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use and to track your engagement with us.

### Non personal information

Redgate may share non-personal aggregate or summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, such as information relating to the number of users linking to our website from their sites but Redgate does not sell or share any information at the individual level.

### Cookies

Cookies are very small text files saved to your computer used to track user navigation around a website.

At Redgate session cookies are used when users log-in to the website. Redgate will use such cookies to identify unique users to our websites. They are not cross-referenced with any other information such that an individual person could be identified.

Redgate use tracking cookies track your movement within our websites, and your engagement with our other services such as blogs and newsletters. You'll receive this cookie when you visit one of our websites but the information it collects will remain anonymous until you share your email address with us through one of our websites.

Redgate may use a third party to serve advertisements on our websites. The advertisers may use cookies to track the number of users responding to the campaign. Redgate does not have access to or control of cookies placed by third parties.

Disabling/Enabling Cookies – users have the ability to accept or disable cookies by modifying the settings in their browser. Disabling cookies, however, may mean that some functionality may be affected. For further directions on how to disable cookies please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/stop-cookies-installed.html>

### Disclosures

Other than the disclosures referred to in this policy, we will not disclose any personal information without your permission unless we are legally obliged or entitled to do so (for example, if required to do so by Court order or for the purposes of identifying fraud or other crime).

We will only disclose your personal information to a third party either as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of Redgate and/or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

### Information about our products and services

It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In order to help us do this, from time to time Redgate may send you, with your consent, details of our products and services which we think may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to continue to receive these details, then send a blank email message to [unsubscribe@red-gate.com](mailto:unsubscribe@red-gate.com). You can also unsubscribe from our newsletter by using the 'unsubscribe' option located in each of our newsletter communications.

### Keeping our records accurate

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

### User discussion forums

Redgate may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or other news groups available to its users. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

See information on [use](https://forums.red-gate.com/faq.php) of our forums.

### Security

We have implemented technology and policies to help safeguard your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use. For example, transactions conducted through the website are encrypted and user log-in is subject to password protection. We will continue to monitor and update security measures as new technology becomes available as appropriate to the website.

### Transfers of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area

Information you provide to us may be transferred by us to Red Gate Software Inc. and/or our service providers that are situated outside the European Economic Area (EEA) and may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. Any of our servers may also be temporarily located in a country outside the EEA. If we transfer your information outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected in accordance with EU data protection law.

### Your consent

By using our website, or giving us your details at an exhibition, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Redgate. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we would disclose it.

### Contacting us

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any enquiry relating to your personal information, you can do so by sending an email to us at [privacy@red-gate.com](mailto:privacy@red-gate.com) or by contacting us at Redgate Software Limited, Newnham House, Cambridge Business Park, Cambridge, CB4 0WZ, United Kingdom.

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we store about you (for which we may charge a small fee).

* * *

## Cancellations

In compliance with the Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013, you have the right to cancel an order within 14 days of purchase.

To cancel, please complete our cancellation form, and send it to Red Gate Software Ltd by post, fax, or email.

* * *

## Legal

Red Gate Software Ltd. (No. 3857576) was incorporated on 12/10/1999 under UK law and, where applicable, complies with all UK laws and regulations.

Red Gate Software Inc. was incorporated on 21/1/2011, under the laws of the State of California (US) and, where applicable, complies with all federal and state laws and regulations.
